Welcome to the madness
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up a scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage Queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Scythe twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame
podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up tight boot flashing on cam chat losing air
Yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight Alex try to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still crackin Joe
we're trending in the press welcome to the madness buckle up tight boot splashing on cam chat losing
their minds michael getting gong to alex taking flight it's wild it's wrong and we do it every
night page got him simping hearts in the chat but she ain't got time for a dude like that diamond
flirting hard let the girls react it's a freak show party no filter all facts yeah all facts
The vibe
Ghost, where'd you go?
The song was over, I mean, I know, it was just a couple of minutes.
Uh-oh, where'd you go?
Okay, so yeah, in case you didn't see, like, yeah, ghost
clapped off, app is off the panel.
It's just like, I get nervous with so many people on the panel.
I just want to make sure the show stays up and everything.
I'm gonna start with a new one.
Hey, well!
What's the fuck?
Hold on, this is the last one though.
My open panel, let me choose who can join.
You got it, Ghost.
Tonight is Ghost, so I did promise him an open panel,
his own open panel, and so,
you know, I'll just have to supervise a little bit,
but yeah, it's your choice.
It's your choice who gets to go on and off.
You just tell me.
I'll put my number in the back chat in case, you know,
you're unable to, you want to talk in private
or something like that here.
In case I'm not like right there, okay.
And you need someone to run the panel or something.
Okay, that's my phone number goes.
You can text me.
Yeah, let's go.
Okay, we'll have fun.
I'll just be,
I'll just be a kind of this watching from the back making sure things don't go
too crazy and wow
Intense okay, here we go
Let's go. Let's fucking go. Let's go. Yeah
Your night goes
Okay, yeah
Yeah, but I want you to you know, I do trust you to
Yeah, let's lay I nobody's enjoying but it's fucking go get your money, dude. Oh
Thank you so much goes
Yeah, that's really really appreciate me gosh. This blue. Oh, it's fucking go
Yeah
I'd like
I do have a couple questions. Ah, yeah, so if I donate 100 obviously I sponsored a panel
I'm not gonna make you go all night because you know
But yeah, so it's 25 to kick someone so I open panel obviously, but can I kick people?
Yes, I can I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't I can't
Okay, so you want to do that? Do you want to choose now or do you want to do it throughout the night?
Or how do you want to do it? So you have four people in mind? Okay, let's run it. Let's run it tonight. You know
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Here you go. So we have the young guns in the back which like young guns brought on the stage
Yes, sir
Okay, I'll have to cover the stage in a second. I do need to be fairly by the way our psyche. Let me ask you a question
Why are we having this abathing?
The bastion I mean I
Left
We do have four bombers out because the first of them left right away
But Sebastian joined it. He joined the panel
Where did I see him? Yeah, he joined the panel. He was he's just been here. So it's like, yeah
He's the one that told me to open it up donate and uh him and Goddy were arguing or something like that remember
Yeah
Oh my god, you were arguing it. Yeah
They're kind of like pretending like because the you know the bathroom cup that has to be like spunky speed and stuff like that
And then like it was like what do I get? What do I get for a hundred dollars?
Shake it. Let me just take something twerk. No, I'm just kidding. I was about to do it
I want I do have a couple requests though. Yeah, I want to be able to kick
I want to be able to kick at least two people off and I want to and I want to read you from page at some point
Okay, you want to read yeah, okay? Well, I'm sure
I would say you know work, you know, just talk to page about that
I forgot about the oh, I forgot about the third one. Uh-huh get my second girlfriend off your shirt
You don't like to start well
Is that your girlfriend
Lookin ass boy because perception is it with the perspective leave my girlfriend alone?
You really like her, huh? You like her? Well, she's just on my shirt. I mean she's not like it's not like, you know
I'm dead. She was like I'm just her gay friend, you know
So what if she's my girl why she on your shirt?
Because we're it's like just like no
I've beat a tattooed on me, too, and it's like even we're not dating. You know, it's like it's just another love
I was walking home now. Where you got that tattooed at?
What again? It's actually part of the not far from here. I walked through it. Actually
No, I'm talking about on your body. We're gonna get it up you that. Oh
You haven't seen it. Oh, hold on
No, I'm gonna put your shirt back
Okay, okay. So we have the MF is back backstage or like the MF on the show. I
Don't know. It's your piano
He was on earlier, right? Was any on earlier?
Okay, let's make sure
Hello, if you're if you if you're okay with it. I'm down. I'm down. I'm down. I'm here
here
You know
I don't hear anything. Do you hear him?
I don't hear shit. I don't hear him. Okay, so I'm gonna take off the thing
I'm getting kind of like nervous because it's like I'm just a few people
I think people are like wanting to meet poem. BMF. Are you there?
I don't do not hear you if you get to talk to the next 10 seconds or I will just be backstage come back when you're
Beautiful
Right. I don't know. How you guys doing? How you guys doing? Good. Yeah, let them out. Let them out. Okay, good
Well, I'm gonna leave the banner up because there's not like there's nobody really on camera. How you doing, sir?
DMF alright, how are you doing tonight?
Oh, I think you have a microphone problem. Yeah, I take that mode. I take them at this point. Okay. Yeah, I mean
Yeah, it's like doesn't make any sense really
He did it and he's like but then he's like not answering. Yeah, he did the answer but he wasn't answering after that
Yeah, he wasn't answering before and then he stopped it stopped the answer and it's like, I don't know
It's just like I give a little
We're glad it's gonna try to and I didn't wreck I didn't wreck did you recognize his voice? I didn't know I don't think it was
The MF I don't know that stands for black
Sentences young guns big motherfucker. Maybe maybe that's what maybe and that's where you have to get the MF or
I don't know
I'm gonna be grab a drink
I wish school would join back up because I didn't mean to go over to him like that
But he had his little buddies there kissing his ass, but you know
What I was saying was you you didn't go to a debate school, you know you did
Cuz I've worked your ass easily, but I don't want to whip your ass. I want to hang out with you join
Open panel. I paid a hundred bucks open panel. Yeah for sure school join
You're welcome to come on school. Of course. It's your panel's like yeah. Yeah, but it's like yeah, you know, I mean it's like you
You know, I might have paid for it, but it's
Of course of course it is but I do you want to give you like a little bit of the way tonight because I did promise you
I was like I was like because remember last night. I was like hey ghost
Just like I'll give you another panel to like you have whatever you want on and off
Yeah, I know you did you did you did you did you did yeah, I mean it's like
Now I'll be able to probably get a computer finally
But I'm pretty sure you we all know Alex pretty sure he's the one that told me put my money where my mouth my mouth is and I did
He did he certainly did I think uh, sir
You know, I really am grateful to you and thank you. You know, it's like, you know
Like a cash shop or something. I don't like paying YouTube. I have cats. I can't get that how much does YouTube take for me?
like 30%
Yeah, but it's good to have like good to have like the
Super chat still because I think it helps the algorithm because YouTube does make a little money from it
So they probably don't as it feels good way for like people that are watching it feels good when we can donate
We don't know about anything that we can donate
One YouTube because when I do have a cat because we're on YouTube, you know I'm saying yes
And I do have a cash
People don't it's in my uh, so my shadow shadow shadow. No, it's like it's like it's cash up psyche awakens
It's just a dollar sign psyche awakens and it's just that's the cash app
And that's also another way besides if you want to do it out if anyone wants to say something outside it outside of the
Super chat system. I also paypal to you if you or if anyone or is else here, so I have a few
Fewer ways to pay
$100 bucks or now nobody's gonna join for real nobody in the chat
We're gonna look in the chat. How's the chat? Oh, there's Sebastian in the chat
So Sebastian do you like all the thoughts it goes that goes to the donate Sebastian is more than welcome to come over here
Yeah, goes to have been a you know having this last night member. I had his back. It's got him number
Yeah, and a hundred dollars. Nobody's gonna fucking join really. I'll just say I'll just say
They but they will they will go so you have to give it a little bit of time
You know it's like people will it's just like I think maybe then maybe I think now they're scared
They'll get banned. I think maybe they get scared. They'll get banned for 24 hours or something if they come up
Unless you said some dick I ain't been in no one
Yeah, and I'm not banning. No, and yeah, Memphis Memphis. Yes. He did he just a passion should already it's Sebastian sugar already been up here
Yeah, he is he's super generous. Yeah
Memphis say like he I'm ghost, you know, did give a very large donation the past couple days and so, you know
I'm not would you like it? I'll run it. I'll run it with the comments. Let's go
Okay, run it, run it, and you know what?
Let's run it, let's run it.
You'll have fun doing it, and I'll be here too.
I'll be like, you know, I'll just be like,
I want you to like, kind of like, just like-
Who the fuck is Patrick?
You're the guest of, I'm Patch, I'm P-A-T.
I'm not Patrick, but I'm P-A-T, that's like you.
It's like you, it's like you waking up, P-A-T.
My name's not Patrick, but it's P-
Dude, Sebastian, join us.
We know you like to join.
You joined us last night, and we know you like to join.
Memphis, and Memphis is a good person.
Yes, of course. Memphis is a mod of mine and you know, she
Sebastian is protective of the show that you know ghosts is a good guy ghosts is protected with me
And that's like a lot of people
Kind of like
I gave a hundred dollars come up here brother, please
And Marcy Marcy is always welcome right or
Marcy's welcome of course. Yeah Marcy Sebastian come up here Marcy
By the way, I heard it was like, was it your birthday, Marcy?
It was somebody's birthday.
I believe it was Marcy's birthday recently.
Happy fucking birthday, come up here.
Let's go over there.
Come up here.
No, thank you. The only place
Ghosts can go now. No, but maybe it's like well the ghost is not even that like annoying. I mean, I've seen him get
Fuck are you talking about H a the fuck are you talking about? He's a loud place. I don't know. Thank you real quick
Let me handle this if you don't mind. Do you mind? Yeah, well, let me handle this
What do you mean that what do you mean? This is the only place I can go now
I can go psyche you that you'd have to you'd be forced to I can go many many many places
What the fuck do you mean by that?
If you weren't too fucking stupid to like actually join and tell me that let's have it
Yeah, bye HK
You're lucky. I'm not a fucking rude mother fuck with their ranch
Bring your ass up. What do you mean? That's the only place I can go. What do you mean by why are you leaving?
What come here and fucking debate me then? What do you mean?
I'm sorry psyche, I'm done crashing up
What it's so funny, I just got like it's got you know
Marcy you might as well join
Beautiful. It's not very strange
Message on my on my come up right real quick. Hold on one second. I'm a little bit concerned one second
Oh shit one second Sebastian. Oh my hey, look at the look at your chat real quick. Can you see that?
Yeah, read it read it
Ghost is to be a good guy, but you seem to be a prick. Is that that me or not? Are you a psyche? No psyche. Do you remember when I?
Donate money to you and open up the panel because
Sebastian was arguing with the God he because
Fucking Sebastian asked me to have his back. Do you remember that? Yep?
And now how am I a bad guy? I fucking donate it to open the panel. I donate to have your back
Mean the fuck you talking to us Sebastian if you're too fucking stupid that or you might can I say the word?
You might be too retarded to have the fucking conversations or
How what do you mean by that? I fucking literally donate I fucking spent money
For you to have even the conversation with God he fucking retarded
Or do you not remember that it was last night I remember
If you're too fucking scared to come up here just be too scared to come up here. That's fine. I'm not gonna judge you
Don't talk shit though boy. I
Fucking donate it literally. I've done it. How much I donate well fuck it. How much well fuck it
Donate a lot of money for you to come up here and talk shit
Sebastian you're just too fucking stupid to have the conversation. You're like, hey get him get got he get got he get got he's
Don't I don't feel like you're bored. I feel like you're retarded. You're the little trouble-causer and
Then you run to me when we get in trouble
Fucking retard
Sebastian I am generous I I literally gave you last night retard. I let you talk to
All right, I'm finna crash I was like yeah, I'm a let's run it. I'm gonna have to crash out
Sebastian you're you're a piece of shit. You don't the fuck you're talking about
Nobody try to challenge you. I gave you said you were bullied. I defend you. You told me who your bully was I fucking
Debate him now. You're too scared to go up here. And since you're too scared to come up here
You're gonna talk shit to me. You're gonna talk shit to me really
Fuckin bag it. All right. Go ahead. It's like he
Come on up guys
Panel is open. You want to come up? Fuck you
Come back up. You can come back up. He said he's even back up Sebastian
Fuck what school school but fuck you Sebastian. How about that made me fucking pay money
Made me talk shit about Goddy. What you know, I love you
You bring all you ran that mouth. Hey last night psyche. Did I not have Sebastian's back? Do you remember that?
Yes, you did. I'm not debate for the did I not debate for him. You remember that?
Yes, now you're gonna talk shit in the fucking comments fucking now you're gonna talk shit in the comments fuck you
Yeah, I did one of them up not now you fucking retarded fuck you
School you're more than welcome to join if you want
Fuck you Sebastian
Hey Sebastian, can you do you can you take this I'll give it to you real quick this little guest
Can you take this and fuck off you retard?
Mr. Hey goes, please come get golly. He's bullying me and I fucking came here
You know what school I give another $10 if you're not all back on
Fuck you Sebastian by the way, bitch
Ain't nobody gonna outdonate me and nobody gonna out the day he has no better very please
Hey psych, thank you
You hear me brother
Take these not important at all. Hey psych. Oh, why you got me up here with Sebastian. Oh
Who's here?
Yo captain you look like
Oh, that's you. I thought you was Sebastian. What's up, Sike?
Oh, that's you. It's sir. Oh shit. What up, man?
It's not sure it's stature. Get it correct here. Okay, so it's a stature Sebastian
Is that all you take they turn there and Sebastian's that's not so bad. That's a fucking porn bar
You sure I can name of a stop talking who's the best
Ghosts I'm here man. I got your back man. What are you talking about?
Can I go I paid a hundred bucks and I got one to be one against him you're
I was talking about that Memphis person earlier man. She's talking about you
Fuck you. You know the fuck you're talking about
Who's that Memphis person talking all that shit boy? I put fucking paid month for you last night
And you said God he was gonna beat you up. I fucking paid money to make it open. Oh, God
He can't be nobody talking about
You're talking about sir stop asking me you don't the fuck you're talking. Oh it goes. I got your back, man
Don't worry. I think you're misunderstanding the situation. No fuck you know bitch. You were just talking shit in the comments retard
No, I'm talking about Memphis. I'm talking about Memphis that Memphis. No, look at no look at the comments. You fucking dumb dumb
Where with you better realize you better fuck your talk to do you better realize who the fuck it
I can tell you like this now, sir
You can better realize you the fuck you're talking talking about a I'm talking about that Memphis person
And I meant this person I can grab about you and I got your back man
I'm just the only one that's got your back
You and fuck your back. I had your back last night bitch. You know how that went
You're a fucking bitch. Oh, yeah, I think you're getting something wrong here, man
I was that I was saying that Memphis person sounds like a prick not you know
You're a fucking retarded. You don't the fuck you're talking about if you stupid they have the conversation
Oh, no, man. Yeah, you got it wrong man. We're talking about something wrong with you. You might be retarded
you might fucking be stupid
are you drunk right now?
what's going on with you?
I don't get it
I explain it to you
I said Memphis
that Memphis person
is talking about you
what's your name?
just call me Seb
yeah, Seb
you're fucking
you don't know what the fuck
you're talking about
sir
what should I call you?
should I call you?
what do you want to be called?
at this point
you should probably call me daddy
Oh, you're misunderstanding something that I'm talking about that Memphis
Not gonna protect you
I'm talking you said come protect me from Goddy. No, I never asked you to protect me man. What are you talking about?
We have to do evidence you fucking retard. Oh, no, you're putting words in my mouth. I never asked you for nothing
I don't need nothing from anyone man. Me. I stand on my own two feet by myself, man
I'm talking about that Memphis person earlier, man. I think you're too drunker. I don't know what's going on
Man, man, man, you don't only want to head your back. What are you talking about?
I'm the only one who had your back and I barely know you man. I've known you for maybe a week
You're talking too much
You did ask me for help, by the way. You said come save me from God because I guess God use them
No, no, I didn't say nothing man. We talking to I'm talking to everyone. You don't care. I don't need anyone's help
You did that. No, I said I said you're the only one that makes sense up there, but now you're not making any sense right now
I think you're drunk. Tell me the truth. How many beers did you have?
Sir, I'm going against you you retard how much how many beers you drink
What's going on here, man? Are you?
Don't ask me for help you don't listen man. I don't need this crap man. Listen. I had a long day
Yeah, I don't need this crap. I don't know what you're doing. I give a fuck
You don't seem to make any sense. Are you drunk or what's going on with you right now?
I don't care. I paid a lot of money for you last night. I know I've seen that man
I've seen that you say about 300 bucks and today's
You spit my fucking face
What are you talking about? I'm telling you again for like a tenth time. I had your back
I'm talking about a Memphis person that Memphis person in the chat
What are you talking about? I got your back you idiot. What are you too drunk to realize that stay on your own then man
And you don't want my friendship fine. You lost my friend. You're right. Bye. He's keep wasting your money
I ask you real quick can ask you one question though. Why would you ask for why would you ask for my help?
You said hey get God what you did say that
Why'd you say that?
Yeah, cuz you know better hey stop talking to me boy fucking retard
Stop talking to me Sebastian fucking dumb dumb
Fuck it. I'll give it another hundred dollars. Do you shut the fuck up?
Okay, so it goes we now have we have jaytee stay turn and gaudy backstage who to bring up
Not guys
Let god be out rough. Okay. I
Called to God in you. What type of shit is this?
What's that bucks for Sebastian's ass you fucking overpaid
Okay, what do you want gaudy? I know you're gonna talk shit. What do you want?
Well, you know I'm going to talk shit. How do you know I'm going to talk shit?
Because you're fucking retarded, sir.
No, I don't talk shit, okay?
You always talk shit
You all you
God mode, that's what I fucking talk. You got okay. I'm kind of
Right now
I'm giving you a chance
It's an open panel
Don't want
Okay
Please are you good?
All right, we're gonna be cool when a grown man begs. I don't like to see that. Yeah, are you gonna be cool, brother?
I don't want to you
Are you gonna be cool? I'm relaxed. I'm relaxed. Don't repeat yourself. All right
All right, who else like you else wants to join you said a couple names, sorry
Who you got a gaudy in this bitch
I mean GT and stay turned to a backstage
Yeah, I fucking let them both join
Okay
I don't believe
And
Granny
Like he could be in four people
Use this channel give him like a hundred more dollars
Yo, God, what the fuck is going on in him?
Crazy shit, man. He's giving them thousands of dollars for what he's not getting. Yes at the end of the day
It's no psyche's chair this cocksucker can empty his whole bank account. It's still slightly channel ghost
You know how many Filipino bitches you could be getting right now instead of this
5 easy. Oh, that's what I'm wondering like what is he doing? So he straight up gave $100 straight
I didn't see it. I wasn't here. Dude. He's been dude at this point. It's like over $300 in like
He gave 20 then he gave more
100 I just seen him drop the hundred. I just seen him drop a hundred a couple minutes ago
I don't blame him, you know, whatever
We made him leave his own panel
But I guess I guess so
Hey, I think you might have put the fear of God in them you are
What though he was begging to he's like, don't please don't don't do that
You see how you see how he shit on Sebastian was trying to be his quote unquote friend. Yo, you see how Sebastian
yo you see what Sebastian shut the fuck up that's when ghost was like uh i'll pay you more
psyche to make him shut up and he wasn't even talking
i want to see how much ghost will give him like fuck just give him a friend today ghost you just
He stole like he stole like $10,000 from a retired lady
You are I'm gonna make you be me pump
Wait, you're wasting 25 on turn work. I promise you you will waste $25 on being in turn. That's a good prime rib dinner right there
Five dollars. What happened? Yeah, you're slowing down. How did it go from a hundred to five?
Who's here
It is so discussed. Oh my god
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Is it? What?
Are you having a heart attack?
What is she doing?
It's a real woman that if you
It's a bitchy. It's a bitchy.
What do you mean?
What is she doing
She got a titties
Then goes
are you okay? I suck it. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes. He goes
I can't even
You see I can't even say I can't even see that I'm speechless. I'm speechless now
I know I made the right decision to become those glasses like you those glasses are working them don't the headphones the glasses
It's working for you, brother. Oh
My god, I have to give you I have to give a compliment. You know what to do
Oh my gosh. I don't know why she did that. She was laughing. I'm sorry, but she wanted to be called out.
I gave her a lot of money. How many hours we got? I mean, I'm pretty sure what she did soon.
I was sleeping all day, so if you're down to hang out, I can sleep.
Hey, listen, calm down.
Okay, let's do it.
Like he was like, yeah, I'm gonna give you some sugar. Oh my god. It was because it was like I know her because she comes on
She's like that, you know, she's like a really nice. I think it's like midwestern kind of lady
I have something to say a psych real quick. Well, you did see boobies. I know that's traumatic
You know what I'm saying? I mean, I mean, I was like, I don't think it was like this
I know I've never seen it coming up on like the bottom of the bottom of her like moomoo and like she was like
She was like flopping them around. It was so weird. It was I've never seen anything like that. What is it back stage? Oh, no, she's on
That's like God he backs it. Okay. Yeah, I mean I know that I know they're listening. I know they're listening if
They want to kick me off at least so fit me if he's though 50 bucks, I'll leave
Because you said 25 but I throw a lot
They thought 50 I'll leave
What do you what do you ask what they thought it's okay, so so thank you kick you out
Okay, yeah, yeah, okay if they if they if they they're down
Ghost has that offer for you guys and so you know I want to apologize to school
But not really I don't want to apologize because uh, it wasn't my fault. Everybody says that's mr. Debate or so I did try to debate on my bad
Yeah, well
You know so
Okay
Yeah, I'm just a little bit shaken up. I just I don't know what I was looking at. It was it was just
I'm like speechless. I've never seen anything like it. I've never seen anything like that in my life
I don't know which I was like what is she doing?
down to these wifey show I
Don't know she could have done it like she could have like five porn bombers something like that
But she like she stated that maybe she wanted me to see them. I don't know maybe she did
I mean, I'm sorry Vicky. I didn't mean to like dream and like but she I mean she was laughing on my screen
But she was laughing and so but uh, yeah, I'm sorry. I didn't mean it's like it's okay. You know, you're
You're a nice lady. I'm sure you wouldn't do that on the show. Thank you for doing it backstage
Listen, if you would throw 20 bucks, I'll look at him. All right. I'll look at this
Oh my gosh
For $20 for what? Oh, it was scary guys. I've never seen anything like it
I've paid more than you even fucking imagine. So you're not gonna kick you're gonna kick those
Okay. Yeah, it was them. So I'm just a little cheek-sucking up still. I don't know
Wow
I can't see that. I mean, it's like, I mean, she's not there anymore. She left. I mean, after,
I don't know, I've seen for a minute, but she was back, she was doing it the whole time when she
was sitting back there. It was, it was just intense. Maybe, maybe she said like, oh,
Gov's gave some money. I'm going to show my tits and maybe you'll let me up or...
you know, I'm saying maybe she thought it was me.
Okay, Vicky, if you want, Vicky, although you can't really see,
I'd have to have you back, I'd have to clean all backstage,
I'd have to end the show, put them backstage,
and then she'd have to do a, like a free call.
Ah, stay, hey, those ain't that important, go around.
Okay, okay.
Okay, Psyche, is this an open panel or not?
If not, I'll leave. Oh, well, I think tonight...
Who's asking? Who's asking?
State's turn to this, but State's turn,
Crucible Ghost is kind of running the panel tonight because...
You know what, State's turn, State's turn...
Yeah, fuck it. Let's take your come up here if he wants to okay. I'll you guys talk for a minute here. Yeah, yeah
So
Yeah, what's going on go so I'm trying to find out like I get you
Listen, I get you donated so hundred dollars
Cool. Yeah, I mean, but is it still an open panel because Psy keeps asking you
What's going on goes do you want it to be an open panel or you just want one-on-ones all night like what do you want?
Can't got to come up to it. I don't I don't give a fuck sir first
Yes or no, nah, just answer what can they come up whoever's backstage now everybody
No, no, they cannot so what the fuck this is who was one on ones all night
So you're here right now. What do you want?
I want you to bring people up here so it could be fun like it with this one. I'm watching this. It's not cool dog
It's not cool
Listen you they're gonna have to promise to be cool or give me some money and I'll fucking open it
No, did I did did I cut you up yet?
I'm talking to you right. I'm talking to you. We're having a conversation. I didn't cut you
Okay, real quick real quick today. Did I let you up here? Yes or no?
Nah, we really goes listen. Yeah
Fuck with you, but fuck you for letting him control your pain
Real right now. I'm about myself pussy. All right. Bye. You fucking retarded
Now, if anybody else wants to come up here and be cool, let's have the conversation.
I thought State Church actually would do it, but that's a disappointment.
Oh, yeah, he was totally disappointed.
I'm not going to let you, Psyche, I am disappointed.
Yeah, I mean, most people think that State Church usually is cool.
He's usually cool.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, it is an open panel. Yes. I don't want you New York people in here, but
Hey, you know, I paid a lot of money
Doesn't mean everybody can come up like it
That's what even though when I had open panels, like sometimes I wouldn't have people want it's gotta get like shit for it, right?
But uh open panels
You know what they could use site they could pay you more than I paid you and they could open right
But they're not they're never gonna do it. Yeah
Yeah, but it's a I mean, it's also they don't
By the way, it isn't on panel. I just don't want those new art people up here here. Okay. Okay. Yeah
And I understand so it's like in the open panel, but it doesn't mean like it's like I have to whatever it's like
That's what I choose
By definition and that open if I paid for it
Yeah, I paid for it. It's not that fucking open. I mean, yeah. Yeah, it's like a good. Yeah, it goes
He did more than
He I don't want to I don't want to speak forms like you
But I think he was making argument like oh so I keep our old ghost when you open up
It's always open panel like that's why you know for it. It's true
I did so when I hear these New York people in your area. Yeah, it's like
There we go. It's like sometimes the estate if stature sends you five bucks right now and says, I'm sorry
I'll let him up. No fuck the five dollars. Fuck that. I'll send you the five dollars if he says
Sorry, I'll let him back up. Got he is back. Do you want got you on?
Yeah, that got you up
Got it. Yeah, I got it. I'm cool. I'm cool. What's that in the gravestone?
Put it on the big screen. By the way, I was just kidding about the five dollars
Happy birthday, Marcy. We need to say happy birthday Marcy. Go ahead. Oh, there we go. Happy birthday
You smell like a shoe, happy birthday to you, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday to you, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr, happy birthday dear Marcy Farr
Yeah, why is that? Why is marching up here? I don't know. She's afraid of you. You've been terrorizing everybody all night
With that I haven't terrorizing one sir. I just made a lot of money. You're throwing your money around like you're on the place. I
Don't own the place. This is I've made it very clear. This is cycles panel
The psyche doesn't want me here. You know what psyche can do. It's got it's a red button. He could push it
What was the deal you made just now? I wasn't here. I just got here about five minutes ago
What was it then you're not here? Hey, uh, uh, let Marcy up here Marcy. You want to join?
I'm done talking to you by the way unless you want to fucking you want to talk about it
Well, I'm not talking to you Marcy come up and get your present
Okay, what what deal did I just make?
Yeah
I didn't I did I didn't just give money. So what do you it's
You gave thank you a hundred dollars. You want a piece of his ass. That was the how long
You gave my hundred dollars for a piece of his ass
Buddy
I didn't lose nothing. I destroyed you on your own panel. Well, talk, you know
I lost a couple brain cells. I didn't lose nothing here on four eyes. I'll put on anything
Don't be so cheap Oh
Would you like me to actually show you what $100 means?
Yeah, go ahead
Godie you're gone psyche get him gone. Where's the hundred bucks?
Now Sebastian if you would like to apologize you can come back up
Actually, it's like yeah, I don't know if we should that's a bash no
You to behave yourself. I think you I love you. Got you. I love you. Got you. You know, it's like I think that
That's what a hundred bucks does dumb fuck earn it before you talk
So he's like
Okay, well, no, we're good
Still and it's kind of like a quieter. Well, you know what I actually didn't want him to leave but he's
Show me what it means. I mean, I
Know you did he dares you you know, I think he'll I think I don't think he meant it
I think you should apologize. I think that would be necessary. I think I think that would be nice
Well, I don't I don't know how kind of luck you're gonna happen with that, but you know, yeah
Yeah, he doesn't even like to join me. He's gonna happen. They didn't happen
But yeah, I got it. I got it
Wow, it's like yeah, I thought I thought God he was God
Well, you know, I
Think the only one that's got is God and God in the hundred bucks. I guess I turn in the God here
Well, you know
Not only God is this early money. Some people do think God stands for gold oil and diamonds. Yeah, I'm being yeah
I'm being nice. I want to crash up, but I'm not gonna do it. I want to crash on Goddy. I'm not gonna do it
Well, that's good, you know, you're control here. You're actually like really progressed as a you know, because you used to
Be a little bit more hot-headed and now you're like
that's literally what they said to me for the cash-out
hmm
yeah
well
and you know what
anybody else want to join so keep anybody in the back chat
Dark night. I spoke to why am I doing what to people? What do you think?
No, God is a bitch he knows is a bitch
Hey God, did you see what a hundred bucks does you dumb fuck?
Yeah, because he did be ghost and I did talk about it and he's you know, he agrees like he could kick a couple people with that tonight, so
But just is it just for tonight, right? It's just not for 24 hours, right?
Well, what else cuz if you feel like I'm ruining the panel you're more than welcome to join
Maybe you can save it if you fuck on bringing it
Go ahead. What's good?
And it's okay. He'd be totally paper. Do you got it? This is like, you know, it's like
This is how they can join again if he wants, but by the way, Sebastian, you're a fucking bitch
I should have never paid last night. I should have never had your back
Sebastian's a bit psyche
Straight up
Well, yeah, he's talking shit in the chat right now
Yeah, he's talking shit, and you remember all I did for him last night, but I have fucked that, you know
Yeah, I don't know what people are
I don't understand people
I think we would agree. Oh, did he grace you?
No
You know, he's real fashion year
I think psyche with a would allow it on his it's his panel so fashion if you want to join and talk about
I want you how I tried to fucking defend you and now you're talking shit. Please join. Let's run it
Or you're just gonna sit there in the comments and shut the fuck up
Yeah
It's funny that I could run their mouth in the comments, don't they
Yep, they do. I mean, it's like, yeah, they don't come up on stage either
And it's like they should be
that
It's okay. Can you post a psyche real quick in the chat real quick? Can you post the link?
Okay, yeah
Understand like yeah, it's like I'm right here like watching the show and stuff. It's like that. I know what's going on
So it's not like you know, I'm letting him
I'm letting him
Why not what is have your experiments?
Um, yeah, anyway guys, you don't have to like, you know, if you're just being a hater of me
You don't have to be here, you know, it's a there's a lot of other shows you can go to, you know
Well, Amanda, you know, you know, you have you have a lot of the money you could pay to pick me off like I just stole
So if you're tired of me, hey fucking pay $30. I
Paid a lot more than you but if you pay 30, I'll fucking leave
Don't know Pat
My microphone, I'm just trying to fix my mic. Hey, yeah, you try to be like
Glasses are working, bro
You tried to pay last night for are you mad about what? What's wrong? What's wrong Amanda?
I'm not the only one tired of you
I tried to pay you last night and Steki said no, oh try to pay ghost. Oh, what I said no, I don't remember that
Everyone's well. I don't think she tried to pay anything. I think I paid a lot more than
I don't know. I don't know what she's talking about this is there that I hope we're okay, uh, okay, man
You know, it's a guy
Okay, it's crackly
Let me show you should I show them how to do it? It's easy
Oh god, he wants a card
Would you like me to show you I do it's very simple, I'll show you I do it. All right, I'll show you
You did Amanda, I don't remember that I don't remember that
But maybe maybe I was I don't know that or something
I'm not trying to like then I'd have to refund him and plus I don't have it's like it's through like the super chat
So I can't refund him and so it's just the whole thing so
Anyway
I'll be right back guys